were you born with a minute or mindset
we're about to find out if not you're
going to inherit the tricks to do so
were you going with a Lambo probably not
that's why I'm giving away my Lambo
completely for free so make sure you
guys join the Discord so you know all
the instructions how because the
competition to win the lambo for free is
about to start so I'm gonna get a detail
tomorrow move the poker table to the
left and then store it in the garage
until the winner comes and I hand you
the keys and you drive off so make sure
you guys watch this video to the end
because I talk more about that and
there's loads of wisdom in it don't mind
the audio camera guy in the back the
audio in this video but there's loads of
value in this video so make sure you
guys hit that subscribe button unless
well all due respect
your motivation is the key to success
and I think it is the number one
millionaire mindset automation
is when I had a job wasn't making money
was paying in my industry in my Niche I
was constantly searching for motivation
to get me out of this like depression
mindset to get me out of the darkness
that I was in in the tunnel so I get how
many of you guys can use motivation as a
way to I think you're going to get
closer to success the only way I would
use motivation is for simply a
testimonial and confirmation that what
you're doing right now for your journey
is the correct thing but
motivation this spin is what's going to
engulf a 100 motivation every single
time because seeing all these success
stories constantly of people or
purchasing things for themselves cars
watch of houses gifting their family
paying off that all of this stuff is
amazing it is great and it is possible
but by being motivation it's not going
to get you there because after a while
we've constantly seeing these success
stories and nothing is happening towards
you you almost kind of feel depressed at
a point and seeing all of these other
successful people buy cars watches
gifting people paying off their families
that all of these insane motivational
stuff it's cool but that's not going to
get you successful it's just going to
get you hyped for a day or two and then
it pretty much just dies down the only
thing that keeps you going forward and
it keeps that hype going it is
discipline you kind of have to be a
little bit crazy while you're going
through those dark nights you're going
through those lonely roads in that sort
of by yourself to keep going at it
because only the week are the ones that
stop the people that are disciplined and
they stay true to their rules they keep
going while everything gets hard and
that is why success is not for everybody
because nobody's just gonna do the hard
thing everybody wants to do the easy
things so for me discipline engulfs all
of that motivational [__] because it
is only temporary this spin is the true
key to success and real millionaire
mindset have because that is something
you're either born with because you know
what there's only one option that is to
succeed there is no such thing as a loss
it is just a lesson or you have to
develop it and the only way that you
develop it it is staying consistent with
your discipline following your routine
your daily life habits whether it's
being healthy gym whatever the case is
and whatever your Niche is it is staying
consistent and disciplined to it not
just treating it as a side puzzle
nobody's gonna get rich off a side
bustle so discipline is my number one
millionaire mindset strip with
discipline comes routine and that is my
next millionaire mindset Street you're
pretty much not born with it you have to
create you're not born with a routine
you have to literally build it whether
that's waking up brushing your teeth uh
doing push-ups and imaging whatever your
routine is you have to stay true and
discipline to it moment that I started
my career and I started trading there
hasn't been one single day in my career
where I don't do the same exact thing
it's very simple I wake up in basic
brush routine and I walk straight into
my office and I'm in my computer before
9am because I wanted to see the market
open I do my four top analysis on the
pairs that I'm interested in trading and
then I stay in front of my computer
until 11AM which is pretty much once New
York session starts slowing down I have
done this every single day for the past
five years it hasn't been one day where
I don't do it this literally forces me
to see the same thing every single day
you're gonna tell me you do the same
thing in every single day you're not
going to see a pattern that's how I
built my Edge and I found my strategy
and trade obviously with a bunch of
errors and a lot of losses and a lot of
lessons that I learned but it's the
routine and the discipline that led me
to my success perfect example they say
right now you have no idea how to clean
a basket if you just throw it to
basketball whatever basic foundations
right you have no idea how to shoot it
you're the numbers like this about to
say but whatever the case is but if you
build a routine and you stay disciplined
to it where every single day you're
going to wake up brush your teeth go
downstairs and just take 10 shots for
the first week you probably won't make
any shots for the second week you
probably still won't make any shots but
now you're hitting the backboard getting
closer to the rim you're getting better
every single day if you do this for a
period of six months I can guarantee you
you wake up every single day brush your
teeth that you take 10 basketball shots
now you're not going to miss all 10 to
look you'll make one you'll make two and
that is the secret to success it is the
discipline and the routine and doing the
same thing every single day because very
interesting your mistakes and work
consistently following the plan you
can't cheat the grind there's no way
around it you get to stay true to your
breath
millionaire mindset were you born with
it let me warm up and worry about fend
up
[Music]
create rather than consume I realized
when I started my journey that I was
consuming more information rather than
doing something creating something with
it I personally myself was always
consuming these videos of people doing
cold plunges and never took action they
would say it's good for your health it's
gonna remove soreness it's gonna make
you more active and I consume some
information that didn't do anything with
it then realizing that I decided wanted
to just flip a switch and with that
information actually create creating
what I was supposed to be doing the
whole entire time wrapping it and then
consuming so a lot of us we watch all of
these motivational videos all of these
millionaire videos educational podcasts
and we don't do anything with them so a
big key to having a millionaire mindset
is having action creating rather than
consume because if you simply don't do
anything with the information it's
pretty much useless you didn't be just
wasting your time so when I say you are
watching a podcast and you want to make
your your own or be a guest and one do
whatever it takes create it don't just
consume the information and do nothing
with it a true millionaire mindset never
set us now talking about never settle
I'm actually giving away my number click
this video right here but when you're
going to be giving my everything away
for free uh nobody in this industry
nobody my age I'm 22 years old I've ever
seen giveaway at ampergy
and this is something that is exactly
perfect for this point right here
because it'll show you to never settle
and never be satisfied there's a big Pro
those are very big Cons with this
because you're never satisfied in some
means you're never happy to wait but
it's good because it keeps you working
towards something so if you guys aren't
subscribed make sure you guys and
subscribe uh to the channel we're trying
to get to 100K my last video I'm giving
away my Lambo because it was my 100th
video so imagine what we get at 100 000
subscribers so make sure you guys
subscribe it's up to the point of never
studying I say the reason why I've
achieved all the materialistic things
what a lot of people aspire to be a
symbol of success is because I'm
constantly studying new goals I'm never
set it so I remember when I first wanted
to get my first Supercar which was my
rdr8 as I'm about to get it as I know
I'm a monster to a way of getting it I
picture myself already inside of it I
picture myself as I already have it and
I'm already setting the new goal so they
put in simple terms when I was looking
to get my R8 I wanted the R8 because
that was going to get me one step closer
to the mechanic so the re was just a
simple gateway to get to the mechanic so
once I get into the McLaren I understand
that I'm there because of the R8 but I'm
already looking at the next car I
understand that the reason why I'm
getting the canary is to make to get the
next car which is the Rose I want to get
the rolls I understand that the rose is
to get me to the next car which is the
number that I have so every single
achievement that I do materials thing
car example Wise It's to just get me to
the next goal not every single thing
that I get is like wow this is a big
deal this is great now that this is just
getting me one step closer to the next
thing and this gets me well closer step
to the next thing you're not you're not
supposed to treat every single thing
like a big thing it's just supposed to
be the normal every single step to do
gets you closer to the next one at the
second never ending constantly scale and
uh this can kind of be negative in a way
as well because you're almost like a
hamster wheel constantly chasing
constantly trying to find the next thing
that's going to make you happy and I say
I made a mistake never setting him
because I thought everything that I
would get would make me happy but since
I was never satisfied it never fulfilled
that like that enjoyment and just never
fulfilled it because I treated it as
something so normal about I didn't have
a positive effect of me because I'm
working for the next thing so now I kind
of have to shift my mind say another bit
and realize that everything that I'm
working towards has a purpose and the
mainly the purpose is just you guys the
community the viewers the followers
that's why I just that's why I get back
so much I do all these events and on
stuff and that's my new thing so I've
never said it not saying oh I have the
house I'm the card Julie I have the
money I'm just gonna chilling out go to
the beach and live my life no now my
purpose is getting back to you guys so
constantly setting the new bar and
looking for the neat thing to work for
it because you never ever and the one to
seven the moment you're comfortable that
is probably one of the most dangerous
things I think for a man I didn't set
such a turn off just saying that well
like I'm good where I'm at like bro I
don't want to be around like none of my
boys would ever say that [__] to me
because I'm just like yo Mike you're
happy what do you mean you're good where
you're at like how does that how does
that keep you going every single day
that you wake up and want to wake up but
okay do these things so a very important
millionaire mindset is never settlement
you're constantly raising the car and my
last and most crucial point that it
could completely sabotage every single
person entrepreneur Trader it is
comparing yourself to others it is
literally you
versus you you have to compare yourself
to where you were yesterday and that is
it you use other people as a form like I
said a testimonial or a way to use it as
motivation to keep you going but it is
you versus you the goal is for you to be
one percent better than you were
yesterday and I don't think you guys
understand how powerful that is you
might have heard it before one percent a
day if you want to compound it you could
if you don't you don't but that is 365
percent better in one year there's no
investment out there that's going to
happen that type of return so imagine
how you are today and where you can be
one year from now 300 percent better
you're literally double of where you are
now personally myself if you were to
look at my chart of where I was four
years ago and where I am now that p l
chart will start very very plateau and
then once the compound starts hitting
you see the growth the immediate
immediately so for me is don't focus at
these little gains down here just know
and have the bigger picture and just
compare yourself to where you are now if
right now your Fitness you want to start
trading e-commerce whatever the case is
do the same routine and stay disciplined
to it for simply six months and after
the six month period look back at where
you were at the beginning and I can
guarantee you 100 if you stay
disciplined and you were consistent you
were a completely different person that
you were from there if you guys like
these type of videos make sure to drop a
comment below like comment and subscribe
let's get the channel to 100K if you
guys like the style make sure to stay
tuned because I have a lot of new videos
coming towards your way I'll see you
guys in the next video